Here we’re making a distinction,
我们在区分
we’re defining, connotating,
在定义
we’re increasing the connotation of what is meant by ‘heart’,
强化“心”的内涵
[Robinson Crusoe | Desert Island of Ego]
漂流记|假我的沙漠孤岛
because from a mundane point of view
从世俗眼光来看，
in the 7th chapter of the Bhagavad-gītā Kṛṣṇa says,
《薄伽梵歌》第七章Krishna说
bhūmir āpo ’nalo vāyuḥ khaṁ mano buddhir eva ca
bhūmir āpo ’nalo vāyuḥ khaṁ mano buddhir eva ca
ahaṅkāra itīyaṁ me bhinnā prakṛtir aṣṭadhā [Bg: 7.4]
ahaṅkāra itīyaṁ me bhinnā prakṛtir aṣṭadhā (Bg: 7.4)
He outlines sequentially what are the eight material elements:
他按顺序说明了八大物质元素
bhūmir āpo ’nalo vāyuḥ [Cc: 2.6.164],
bhūmir āpo ’nalo vāyuḥ (Cc: 2.6.164),
earth, water, fire, air, ether, mind, and intelligence,
土、水、火、气、以太、思维和才智
and ahaṅkāra— false ego.
以及错误的小我（ahankara）
In the following śloka He says,
在接下来一节诗里他说，
apareyam itas tv anyāṁ prakṛtiṁ viddhi me parām
apareyam itas tv anyāṁ prakṛtiṁ viddhi me parām
jīva-bhūtāṁ mahā-bāho yayedaṁ dhāryate jagat [Bg: 7.5]
jīva-bhūtāṁ mahā-bāho yayedaṁ dhāryate jagat (Bg: 7.5)
He says that, “But the jīva, jīva-śakti …
他说，"但是个体灵魂(jiva)
(what I’ve just outlined is prakṛti—mundane energy)
刚列举的是世俗能量(prakriti)
jīva is a superior type of  śakti,
但是个体灵魂(jiva)是种更高的能量(sakti)
which is above these eight elements.”
超越这八种物质元素。”
So although we don’t normally think of it this way, it’s not the first verse
虽然我们平时不会这么想
that would come to our mind in terms of sahajiyāism.
谈及sahajiyaism模仿主义也不会首先想到这点
Śrīla Guru Mahārāj used it as a refutation of  sahajiyāism.
Srila Guru Maharaj用此来驳斥模仿主义
Along these lines that their idea is that by reconditioning
他们的想法是通过重新调整思维模式
the element of mind, the mundane element of mind,
调整世俗元素的思维
filling it with images of Kṛṣṇa,
让它填充满Krishna的画面
making it accustomed to hearing certain sounds,
让它习惯于特定的声音
that one will have some sort of epiphany,
这样你就会突然开悟
and their swarūp will manifest.
本源的身份(swarup)也将展现
Guru Mahārāj is of the opinion that all of this must dissolve.
Guru Maharaj的观点是，所有这一切必须消释
Because the subtlest aspect is ahaṅkāra, false ego,
这其中最精微的是错误假我(ahankara)，
but then the buddhi, the mind,
但同时，才智（buddhi）、思维
the body that’s housing these elements—
以及承载这些元素的躯体
all of these must be dissolved.
所有这一切必须得消释
In what way? Or … Gurudev gave a famous lecture called
怎么消释呢？Gurudev有次著名的讲座叫
“Dissolving the pillars of ego.”
溶解假我的支柱
“Demolishing the pillars of ego.”
拆除假我的横梁
How? Not through some Buddhistic type of dissolution,
怎么做呢？不是通过佛教那种消融
but rather through service,
而是通过服务
through service engagement, through dedication.
置身于服务，奉献
Biological expression of the soul’s delusion is the body.
躯体是灵魂展现出的生物形式的幻觉
It’s the outcome of jīva’s exploiting tendency,
是由于个体灵魂jiva的剥削倾向
the desire to lord over matter.
想控制物质的欲望造成的
Sometimes he would quote “Robinson Crusoe”.
有时他会引用《罗宾逊漂流记》中
Alexander Selkirk, the famous … The man shipwrecked on the island.
主人公遭遇海难留在岛上
And he has a line, where he says, “I am the lord of all I survey.”
他说，“目光所及，莫非吾土”
“This mood, this mania that I’m the master
这种态度，这种凌驾一切的狂热欲望
and detesting the very notion of …
厌恶任何服务精神，扩展来说奴隶
being subordinate, being submissive.”
拒绝从属，拒绝臣服
In modern times any qualities associated with this notion
这些品质在现代社会是被认为不利的
So the body is a biological expression of the soul’s delusion,
躯体是灵魂展现出的生物形式的幻觉
that includes mind, intelligence,
包括思维才智
but the outcome of exploiting tendency,
是剥削性带来的后果
the biological outcome
剥削性结果以生物形式表达
if we become connected to the service plane,
如果我们能连接到服务的层次
if we withdraw from being exploiting agents
不再剥削而成为充满奉献的个体
then the body, mind, intelligence,
那么躯体、思维、才智
which were the outcome of the exploiting tendency,
这些剥削性造成的后果将开始消逝
begin to manifest—the swarūp.
我们原本的形象swarup开始展现